ACWA's Union Label Department Records 5619/039
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ACWA's Union Label Department Records
1931-1975
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Union Label Department
5619/039
15 cubic feet
15 linear feet
Correspondence, reports, publications.
This collection consists of correspondence, reports, and files from the Union Label Department of Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America.
6826804
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff
Date completed:
June 21, 2010
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, July 2010
Biographical / Historical
The Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, the most significant union representing workers in the men's clothing industry, was founded in New York City in 1914 as a breakaway movement from the United Garment Workers. Radical and immigrant workers in the tailors' and cutters' locals were the core of the seceding group, which advocated industrial unionism and economic strikes in opposition to the UGW's craft organization, which they saw as conservative and timid. Their diverging views had come to the fore during the historic 1910 dispute at the Chicago firm Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. The opposition called the strike against the UGW leadership's advice, and reached a path-breaking agreement with management that established an arbitration system to settle disputes.
Members flocked to the new union. Around 50,000 strong at its founding, by 1920 the ACWA counted about 170,000 members. Initially composed mostly of immigrants of Jewish European descent with Socialist leanings, the ACWA quickly welcomed members of a great number of nationalities and diverse backgrounds. Like in other garment unions, most workers and many members were women, but the leadership was predominantly male, a situation that did not change for many decades. Early on the union adopted a centralized administrative structure combined with industrial unionism, with the joint boards' by-laws having precedence over those of locals.
Espousing a philosophy perhaps brought over by its early immigrant socialist members, the Amalgamated went beyond bread and butter issues and adopted a distinctive form of social unionism that was largely absent in the American labor movement. Starting in the 1920s, it provided educational opportunities and recreational facilities for its members, as well as services such as an insurance plan, banks offering personal loans at low interest rates, low-cost housing cooperatives, medical clinics, and even union-owned restaurants.
Sidney Hillman was the first president of the new union and the most important officer in its history. He applied his experience as bargaining representative in Chicago to the whole industry. Under his leadership the union made significant strides in securing better wages and working conditions for its members, and at the same time it consolidated gains and provided stability to the industry through the widespread adoption of the arbitration system tested at Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. Hillman paid close attention to industry issues, such as production, pricing, and marketing. In order to help management meet the competition of non-union firms, the union conducted studies of efficiency, work methods, and factory costs. Letters to the official publication of the union, Advance, document the controversy that ensued within the union over what was perceived to be collaboration with management.
Hillman also understood the importance of labor's involvement in national affairs and political action. In the 1920s the ACWA sent delegates to the Conference for Progressive Political Action and to the Farmer-labor party conventions. Although many members and officers were Socialists, the union stopped short of officially endorsing the party. Communist attempts at gaining influence within the union were firmly curbed. Hillman's participation in national affairs and politics became prominent during the New Deal, when he became a close advisor to Franklin D. Roosevelt on labor and economic issues. He also served on the board of the National Recovery Administration. Later, during World War II, he helped establish the Labor's Non Partisan League. He was also named associate director of the Office of Production Management, which assisted in mobilizing the nation's resources for the war effort. Hillman's prestige perhaps reflected the healthy condition of his union, which by the end of the conflict was strong and stable.
During the post World War II period the union faced a number of significant challenges. Membership continued to grow (peaking at 395,000 in 1968), but the union's political influence and visibility in national affairs declined. In their never ending pursuit of lower production costs, many firms relocated to the South, forcing the union to engage in large organizing efforts. Simultaneously, signs began to appear of changes that would lead to the almost complete demise of the domestic apparel industry and, ultimately, to the erosion of union membership. Foreign imports of cheap clothing goods steadily grew in the 1950s and 1960s, and mushroomed in the following two decades, plunging employment in the apparel sector into a steady decline. Union efforts to stem the tide included Buy American campaigns and extensive lobbying in Congress, but they were to no avail. In 1976, the ACWA merged with the Textile Workers of America to become the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Despite successful and much publicized nationwide actions such as the Farah boycott and the J.P. Stevens corporate campaign, the woes threatening the union's existence continued unabated. The fate of the domestic industry was sealed in the late 1970s and the 1980s by the flight of firms chasing tax breaks and cheap labor abroad. By 1995, when ACTWU voted to merge with the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, their combined membership was 350,000. The new Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE!) seemed poised to infuse new life in a troubled union.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related collections: 5619: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America And all other 5619 collections.
Textile industry--New York (State)--New York; Textile workers--Labor unions--New York (State)--New York; Clothing trade--New York (State)--New York; Clothing workers--Labor unions--New York (State)--New York; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Union Label Department; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union --Archives; Union of Needeltrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE) --Archives; UNITE HERE (Organization) --Archives
6826804
- Raffle Winners. Suits, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- List of names to be removed from tapes and checked, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Union label newsletter list, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Raffle winners ties processed, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Advertising union label "Are you undermining", 1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Connections act./Daily News Record, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Conventions Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Follow up, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Procedures, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Conventions, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Scope and Contents
  June
- Conventions, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  April-August
- Union label office procedures, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Advertising labels designs and sketches, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Fairy Tale District, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Material Requested, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Newsletters Staff, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  July
- Personnel-Accepted by Union Label Dept. and resumes of applicants interviewed, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Printing Mimeotronic, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Labels. Union Label, 1958-1968 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Label Letters questions- answers, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Raffle winners suits processed [folder 1 of 2], 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Raffle Winners Suits Processed [folder 2 of 2], 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Raffle Winners shirts Committee [folder 1 of 3], 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Raffle Winners Shirts Committee [folder 2 of 3], 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Raffle Winners Shirts Committee [folder 3 of 3], 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Neck Wear Temp Folder, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Miscellaneous [folder 1 of 2], 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Miscellaneous [folder 2 of 2], 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- All staff, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Staff. Charles Litell, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Staff. Ron Dominici, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Staff. Summer Schools, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Staff. Wiseman, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- To-Scott Spencer, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  September
- Import shirts, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Advertising Reg. IL Progresso, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Advertising Reg. Teachers, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Raffle Winners suits [folder 1 of 2], 1968 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Raffle Winners suits [folder 2 of 2], 1968 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Record retention file suit winners [folder 1 of 2], 1966 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Record retention file suit winners [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Shirt raffle winners [folder 1 of 2], 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Shirt raffle winners [folder 2 of 2], 1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Related mailing list, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Related Mailing list, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Retailer Mailing, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Retailer Mailings Originals, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Retailer Mailing Finished Prod., 1970 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Retailer Mailings Graphic, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Raffle winners completed forms Co., 1968 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Sources of info, 1962-1968 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Manufacturer Carl, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Directories Reg., 1970 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Massachusetts, 1950-1971 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Patents, 1959-1966 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Minnesota- Trademark reregistration, 1959-1970 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Wisconsin- trademark reregistration, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Trademark Connecticut, 1949-1968 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Description of ACWA Garment Label for trademark registration, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Trademark registration Illinois, 1949-1969 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Trademark California, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Trademark Registration amalgamated- blank, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Copyright Application Amalgamated Union labels [folder 1 of 2], 1931-1939 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Copyright Application Amalgamated Union Labels [folder 2 of 2], 1936-1939 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- "A" miscellaneous, 1955-1969 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Advertising requests [folder 1 of 2], 1971 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Advertising requests [folder 2 of 2], 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Negative Advertising Request, 1967-1972 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  Hebrew
- Convention Requests, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Suit, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Ties, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Raffles shirts completed, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Rennie, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Superba, 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Ties on order [folder 1 of 2], 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Ties on order [folder 2 of 2], 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Raffle Winners Suit, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Raffle Winners Suits not complete, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Shirts, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Raffle winners-shirt [folder 1 of 2], 1972 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Raffle Winners- shirt [folder 2 of 2], 1972 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Cal Bellaver- Farah, 1970-1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Anne Draper- California, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Gero, Edith - Farah, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Farah- lithographs [folder 1 of 2], 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Farah- lithographs [folder 2 of 2], 1973 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Joe Smyth Farah, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Erie Richard Lynch, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Richard Lynch - Farah, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Finance Memos - Farah, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Hagger Pants, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Metro, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Metro, 1967-1972 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Metro legal general, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Metro Legal NLRB, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Metro Legal [folder 1 of 3], 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Metro legal [folder 2 of 3], 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Metro legal [folder 3 of 3], 1968 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Metro legal fact sheet, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Metro statements [folder 1 of 2], 1968-1970 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Metro statements [folder 2 of 2], 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Metro photos, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Metro Union Label Gen. Mailing to staff, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Metro Union Label Leaflets, 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Metro Union Label Letters Mail Inter Office and other, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Metro Union Label Publicity, 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Metro Union Label Legal, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Metro Legal, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Metro SBA, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Metro Bonds, 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Metro Union Label Shipping Labels Identification, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Metro Retail Rough Drafts of retail letter., 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Howard D. Samuel Approval And Correction of Metro Retailer letter., 1969 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Metro Retail Legal Approval And Correction of Metro Retailer letter., 1969 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Metro Union Label Letters to/from Retailers, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Metro Retail Response to Camp, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Metro Retail, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Metro Blue Cross, 1965-1969 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Metro Organizing reports- general, 1966-1970 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Metro Union Label Organizing Leaflets [folder 1 of 3], 1969 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Metro Union Label Organizing Leaflets [folder 2 of 3], 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Metro Union Label Organizing Leaflets [folder 3 of 3], 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Metro Union Label Organizing Leaflets, 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Convention [folder 1 of 2], 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Convention [folder 2 of 2], 1973 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Women's rights [folder 1 of 3], 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Women's rights [folder 2 of 3], 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Women's rights [folder 3 of 3], 1971 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Education, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Legislature [folder 1 of 3], 1973 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Legislature [folder 2 of 3], 1973 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Legislature [folder 3 of 3], 1972 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Imports B-H Task Force, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Legal Development "Farah", 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Letters Inter ACWA, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Macys Farah, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- FARAH Memos staff [folder 1 of 3], 1973 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- FARAH Memos staff [folder 2 of 3], 1973 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- FARAH Memos staff [folder 3 of 3], 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Staff Mailing, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- FARAH Kit, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Maurer, Fleisher and Associates, Inc. Our Public Relations Agency: Tom Conway Robert Mauser, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- May Co.-Monitor File, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Letters from MF JS Problem Areas Report, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Cosgrove: Division for Urban Affairs Clergy Catholic Clergy, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- FARAH foreign, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- FARAH financial background, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Finance procedure, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- FARAH Letters - Final and Out, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Endorsements AFL-CIO, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- FARAH Film Premieres, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- International Unions, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Legal Approvals FARAH [folder 1 of 2], 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Legal Approvals FARAH [folder 2 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- FARAH material sent out and act., 1972 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- FARAH memos- to and from with ACW, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- HDS Memos, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Mailing List- FARAH Retailers [folder 1 of 3], 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Mailing List- FARAH Retailers [folder 2 of 3], 1973 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Mailing List- FARAH Retailers [folder 3 of 3], 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Notice of meetings, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- FARAH Staff Meetings, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  March 20,21, 23
- UL Staff Meetings FARAH, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  May 29,30 and 31
- Chicago Meeting, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  May 30
- New York Meeting, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  May 29
- Atlanta Meeting, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  May 31
- FARAH Miscellaneous, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- FARAH Miscellaneous, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- FARAH Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Midwest F Goldstein-Corcoran, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Mintzer Green, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Minutes FARAH Meetings, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- N.O.W, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- National Women's Political Caucus, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- New America Movement, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- FARRAH New England, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Newspaper Clippings- FARRAH, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- International Endorsements other organizations letters, Etc., 1972 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Photos, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Picket Signs (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Printing on order- Material at Graphic, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- P.X.S, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Panchos, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- P.R. -Media and Public Appearance by strikes [folder 1 of 2], 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- P.R. -Media and Public Appearance by strikes [folder 2 of 2], 1973 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- FARAH Press coverage- Labor Press Press Releases, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- FARAH- Press Coverage -General and Trade, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- FARAH- Propaganda [folder 1 of 3], 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- FARAH- Propaganda [folder 2 of 3], 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- FARAH- Propaganda [folder 3 of 3], 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Recap AFL-CIO Boycott (Box 7, Folder 1)
  9/30
- FARAH Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- FARAH Ship info, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- FARAH Situation Reports, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- South, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Southwest. Anderson, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- FARAH Speech requests, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Union Label Speech - FARAH, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Staff and coordinator FARAH, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Scheduling/Advance Striker Tour, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Stockholders FARAH, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- FARAH General (Box 7, Folder 12)
- FARAH Retail (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Boycott History, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- FARAH White Papers (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Local and store comparative report, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Special FARAH Agreement Letters and telegrams, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- FARAH Ads, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- FARAH leaflets and mailings, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Viva la huelga, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- FARAH Fact Sheets, Bulletins, Press, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Alabama, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Alaska (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Arizona (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Arkansas, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- California- CLC of Alameda Co. Oakland, Calif., 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Colorado, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Connecticut, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Delaware, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- D.C, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Florida, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Georgia, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Hawaii, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Idaho (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Illinois, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Indiana, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Iowa--Reg. 14 Dan Healy Chicago Headquarters., 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Kansas, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Kentucky, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Louisiana, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Maine, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Maryland, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Massachusetts AFL-CIO, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Michigan, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Minnesota, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Missouri, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Mississippi, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Montana (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Missouri, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Montana State- AFL-CIO, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Nebraska, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Nevada (Box 8, Folder 33)
- New Hampshire, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- New Jersey, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- New Mexico, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- New York State File # 1, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- New York City File # 1, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- North Carolina, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Ohio State AFL-CIO, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Oklahoma, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Oregon Jess Bell, ACWA, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Pennsylvania, 1971-1974 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Puerto Rico (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Rhode Island, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- South Carolina, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- South Dakota, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Tennessee, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Texas, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Utah, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Vermont (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Virginia, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Washington State AFL-CIO Jim Leary Coordinator, 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- West Virginia, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Wisconsin, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Support: Civic, 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Support: Other, 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  Spanish
- Support - other unions, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Support - ACWA, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Support Reports (from staff), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Staff Dinner, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  April 1
- Labor Statements/ Resolutions, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- FARAH Press Kits, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Helen (Tranquellino) Harris, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Bishop Warren Bourdeaux Statement, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Underground Press (FARRAH), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- United Mine Workers, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  August 15-31
- Student's file, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- T.V. (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Trucking, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- UAW- Michigan Emily Mazey, Sec. ' y- Treas., 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- FARAH Statements and resolutions, 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Weekly FARAH Reports, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- West Draper, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- FARAH Work file, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Warehouse, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- "You are not alone" series, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Southern States Reports, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- F. Penn- VA- MD- N.Y - N.J. Landman- Becker-Stocco-Goldberg- Clair -Corcoran, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Support non-union, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Support, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- DNR, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Note cards (Box 10, Folder 8)
- U.A.W (Del's file), 1973 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Religious Del File, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Center- United Labor Action, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- New York, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- George Watson, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- AFL-CIO Auxiliaries, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Brochures, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Donations, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Winter Campaign, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- AFL-CIO Press, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- PX, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- NOW, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  August 26
- Chicago West Coast Staff MTG., 1973 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  August 28
- UAW, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Weekly Summary- FARAH Staff phone reports (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Texas - Pilot project, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- El Paso materials, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Artha Adair [folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Artha Adair [folder 2 of 2], 1973 (Box 10, Folder 28)